Guide to the A. Poulin Papers and BOA Editions Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- July 1988 Acquisition, 1956-1986; 1; 44.33; (39 boxes)
  - Correspondence and Manuscripts
    - Snodgrass, W. D.
      - "Remains," proofs and related correspondence (Box 9)
    - Whitbread, Thomas: correspondence (Box 9)
    - Wilbur, Richard: correspondence to and from, correspondence regarding reprinting a Wilbur translation (Box 9)
    - Mathieu, Bertrand: correspondence and manuscripts (Box 9)
    - Anderson, Jon: "Death and Friends," folded and gathered sheets (Box 10)
    - Gaulin, Michel: correspondence (Box 10)
    - Hébert, Anne: correspondence, typescript of some of Poulin's translations, circa 1983 (Box 10)
    - Lewisohn, James: poetry (miscellaneous) and attached letter (Box 10)
    - Makuck, Peter: "The Whiting and Other Poems," typescript and attached letter (Box 10)
    - Poulin, Al
      - American Folksong Revival, photographs and related documents (Box 10)
      - "Angelic Order," typescript, 1976 (Box 10)
      - "Begin Again," drafts, 1972-1976; 4 (Box 10)
      - "Contemporary American Poetry," typescript (Box 10)
      - Correspondence regarding Anne Hébert, 2 (Box 10)
      - Correspondence regarding "Elegies" (translations of Rilke) (Box 10)
      - Correspondence regarding "In Advent: Poems", 1961-1971 (Box 10)
      - "Duino Elegies and The Sonnets to Orpheus," proofs, 3 (Box 10)
      - "The Elephant's Womb: A Bestiary of the Will," drafts, circa 1976; 4 (Box 10)
      - Poems, 1974 July 27 - 1974 August 3; 2 (Box 10)
      - Revised poems and translations, circa 1976 (Box 10)
      - Rilke: French poems, translated by A. Poulin, circa 1975; 2 (Box 10)
      - Rilke reviews, circa 1978 (Box 10)
      - "Sonnets to Orpheus," drafts and revisions, 1976; 2 (Box 10)
    - Amorosi, Ray
      - "A Generous Will," typescript (copy) (Box 11)
      - "Marie Guadellajo," typescript (copy) (Box 11)
      - "Panic's Tattoo," typescript (Box 11)
    - Berg, Stephen: "The Red, Red Moon," typescript, signed (Box 11)
    - Clancy, John D. (John Dennis): correspondence (Box 11)
    - Matura, M. Cantius: "Introduction a la Theologie de la Liturgie," typescript (Box 11)
    - Poulin, Al
      - Correspondence regarding Harold Slocum (Box 11)
      - Correspondence regarding Kathy Mezei (Box 11)
      - Essays, published and unpublished, typescript and photocopies, 1966-1968 (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, circa 1975-1978; 4 (Box 11)
      - Offprints: Fiore, Gaulin, Flood (Box 11)
      - Poetry manuscripts and miscellaneous, 1974 May (Box 11)
      - "Poets on Videotape," proofs. Introduction to "Younger Poets," selection for APR II CAP and Ignatow's "Notebooks," notes for review (Box 11)
      - Prose worksheets, 1960-1962 (Box 11)
      - Publicity, circa 1974; 2 (Box 11)
      - Responses to "Contemporary American Poetry" (Box 11)
    - Articles, broadsides, etc. for Folk book (Box 11)
    - "In Advent," stencils (Box 11)
    - Miller, Henry: correspondence (Box 12)
    - Mills, Ralph J., Jr.: correspondence, 5 (Box 12)
    - Piccione, Anthony: correspondence with and regarding, 2 (Box 12)
    - Rosenthal, M. L.: correspondence (Box 12)
    - Simpson, Louis: correspondence (Box 12)
    - Snodgrass, W. D.: correspondence, 4 (Box 12)
    - Stafford, William: correspondence, 3 (Box 12)
    - Stroud, Joseph
      - Correspondence (Box 12)
      - "Signatures," typescript (Box 12)
    - Sutter, Barton: correspondence, 2 (Box 12)
    - Waters, Michael: correspondence (Box 12)
    - Wendt, Ingrid: correspondence, "Moving the House," typescript (Box 12)
    - Wallenstein, Barry: correspondence, including Julien Alberts correspondence, circa 1983 (Box 12)
    - Amorosi, Ray: manuscripts, correspondence (Box 13)
    - Chaplin, William: "Essay son John Logan," typescript (Box 13)
    - Fiore, Peter: "Be-Bop," typescript, correspondence (Box 13)
    - Levertov, Denise: "Oblique Prayers," uncorrected galleys (Box 13)
    - Lieberman, Laurence: manuscripts, reprints (Box 13)
    - Matthews, William: manuscripts, correspondence (Box 13)
    - Poulin, Al
      - "American Poetry Review," appearances (Box 13)
      - "Contemporary American Poetry," manuscripts, 2 (Box 13)
      - "Contemporary American Poetry," original prospectus (Box 13)
      - "Contemporary American Poetry: The Radical Tradition," typescript and related typescripts (Box 13)
      - Correspondence and manuscripts: Makuck and Fiore (Box 13)
      - Correspondence regarding Europe trip, 1983 (Box 13)
      - Correspondence regarding Saint Francis College (Box 13)
      - Correspondence related to and with Younger Poets, 3 (Box 13)
      - Essays (Box 13)
      - "Franny and Zooey," play adaptation by A. Poulin, typescript, 1961 (Box 13)
      - "From Natty Bumppo to Alexander Mundy: The Implications of a Folk Hero's Transformation," typescript (Box 13)
      - Haydn interview (Box 13)
      - Hébert, Anne: Poems, translated by A. Poulin, typescript (copy) (Box 13)
      - Hébert essay, typescript (copy) (Box 13)
      - "In Search of an American Catholic Literature," typescripts, 2 (Box 13)
      - [Marie?], manuscript and notes (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, circa 1983; 2 (Box 13)
      - Notes on poets, typescript (Box 13)
      - Poems, duplicates (Box 13)
      - "Poets and Critics" (Box 13)
      - Reviews (Box 13)
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: "Duino Elegies and the Sonnets to Orpheus," translation by A. Poulin, typescripts (Box 13)
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: "Sketches and Fragments" and "From the French Notebooks of Rainer Maria Rilke," translation by A. Poulin (Box 13)
      - "Saul-Saul," manuscript, typescript and notes (Box 13)
    - Berg, Stephen
      - Correspondence, circa 1978 (Box 14)
      - "O I'm a Human Being: Versions of Eskimo and Tungit Songs," typescript (Box 14)
    - Bly, Robert: correspondence, includes William Lane correspondence (Box 14)
    - BOA Editions
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, circa 1980-1982; 4 (Box 14)
      - Rejections: letters and manuscripts, 6 (Box 14)
    - Cairns, Scott: "The Borrowed House," typescript (copy) (Box 14)
    - Claire, William: correspondence (Box 14)
    - Dickey, James: correspondence, circa 1981 (Box 14)
    - Gay, K. C.: correspondence (Box 14)
    - Stone, Alan: "Love-In the Pentagon," (BOA reject) (Box 14)
    - Guiney, Louise Imogen: "Canisy," by Jean Follain, translation by Guiney (Box 14)
    - Kinnell, Galway: correspondence, circa 1981 (Box 14)
    - Laughlin, James: correspondence (Box 14)
    - Logan, John: correspondence and manuscripts, circa 1979-1983; 4 (Box 14)
    - Lyons, Nathan: correspondence (Box 14)
    - Malanga, Gerard: correspondence (Box 14)
    - Mathieu, Bertrand: "Dion Nittis and the 'Something' That's Missing," typescript and correspondence (Box 14)
    - McClatchy, J. D. (Sandy): correspondence (Box 14)
    - Neale, Vicki L. (Vicki Lewis): correspondence, illustrations for W. D. Snodgrass' "The Führer Bunker" (Box 14)
    - Piccione, Anthony
      - "Nearing Land: Notes from Steerage," typescript, signed (Box 14)
      - "Walls for my People," typescript, signed, with accompanying autograph note (Box 14)
    - Poulin, Al
      - Correspondence regarding W. D. Snodgrass' "The Führer Bunker" (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, circa 1979 (Box 14)
    - Rioff, Suzanne Berger: correspondence, circa 1981 (Box 14)
    - Sackheim, Eric: correspondence, circa 1981 (Box 14)
    - Searle, Leroy: "Minotaur," typescript (copy) (Box 14)
    - Sexton, Anne: correspondence, manuscript (uncollected poems) (Box 14)
      Includes Linda Sexton correspondence.
    - Johnson, Judith Emlyn: correspondence, circa 1981 (Box 14)
    - Flaherty, Doug: correspondence, manuscripts (Box 15)
    - Gauthier, Claude: miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - The Griffin, 1958-1962 (Box 15)
    - Harvard Divinity School: Roman Catholic - Protestant Colloquium program (Box 15)
    - Loyola University: "The Needs and Images of Man," program (Box 15)
    - Maine Commission on the Arts and Humanities: "Prize Poems 1970" (Box 15)
    - Piccione, Anthony: book review, inscribed reprint (Box 15)
    - Poulin, Al
      - Applications for grants, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
      - Correspondence, manuscripts (Box 15)
      - Correspondence regarding Philip Gerber ("Gerbergate"), 2 (Box 15)
      - Medical records, 1974-1976 (Box 15)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2 (Box 15)
    - MOTUS yearbooks, 1963, 1968; 2 (Box 15)
    - Friar, Kimon: correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 16)
    - Kayalis, Takis: "Widow's Taboo," typescript (Box 16)
    - Logan, John: "A Ballet for the Ear," edited by A. Poulin, typescript (Box 16)
    - Plante, David: correspondence (Box 16)
    - Poulin, Al
      - "Contemporary American Poetry," unbound, 2 (Box 16)
      - Correspondence regarding trip to Greece, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1982-1983; 6 (Box 16)
      - "A Momentary Order," typescript (Box 16)
      - "Poem on a Photograph of a Young Painter," manuscript (Box 16)
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: "The Astonishment of Origins," translation by A. Poulin, typescripts, 2 (Box 16)
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: "Journals and Fragments," translation by A. Poulin, manuscript (Box 16)
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: "Orchards," translation by A. Poulin, typescripts, galleys, and correspondence, 5 (Box 16)
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: "Saltimbanques," translation by A. Poulin, manuscript (Box 16)
    - Aridjis, Homero: correspondence, circa 1983 (Box 17)
      Includes Eliot Weinberger correspondence.
    - BOA Editions
      - Advertising material: primarily book catalogues, reviews, 3 (Box 17)
      - Catalogue and prospectus, 1977-1980 (Box 17)
      - Correspondence regarding pamphlet series (Box 17)
      - Correspondence regarding Theodore Stephanides' "Erotocritos" (Box 17)
      - Correspondence regarding W. D. Snodgrass' "The Führer Bunker" (Box 17)
      - Miscellaneous promotional material and reviews, 2 (Box 17)
      - Reviews (Box 17)
      - Signed cards (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Byrne, Edward: signed cards ("Explorers") (Box 17)
    - Gardner, Isabella: "That Was Then," cover proofs (Box 17)
    - Kizer, Carolyn: "Yin," cover proofs (Box 17)
    - [Levertov?], Denise: correspondence (Box 17)
    - Piccione, Anthony: "Anchor Dragging," promotional cards (Box 17)
    - Rosenthal, M. L.: "She," promotional cards, 2 (Box 17)
    - Schaeffer, Susan: correspondence, photographs (Box 17)
    - Simpson, Louis: correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 17)
    - Snodgrass, W. D.: "The Führer Bunker," promotional cards (Box 17)
    - Sutter, Barton: "Cedarhome," promotional cards (Box 17)
    - Whitbread, Thomas: correspondence (Box 17)
    - Wilbur, Richard: correspondence (Box 17)
    - Evangelatos, Constantinos: correspondence (Box 18)
    - Graywolf Press: correspondence, 3 (Box 18)
    - Houghton-Mifflin Co.: correspondence (Box 18)
    - Lee, Li-Young: correspondence, manuscripts (Box 18)
    - Liveright Publishing Corporation: correspondence (Box 18)
    - Mathieu, Bertrand: correspondence, translations of Rimbaud and Cendrars (Box 18)
    - Poulin, Al
      - Book ideas and correspondence, circa 1979 (Box 18)
      - "Cave Dwellers," typescript, notes (Box 18)
      - Correspondence: get well cards, 1974 (Box 18)
      - Correspondence regarding job inquiries (Box 18)
      - Correspondence regarding publications and rejections (Box 18)
      - Correspondence regarding readings, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
      - Correspondence regarding Rilke's French poems (Box 18)
      - Correspondence with publishers (Box 18)
      - Hébert, Anne: "Poems," translation by A. Poulin, typescript (Box 18)
      - List of books purchased, 1969 January - 1971 July (Box 18)
      - Manuscripts, 1967 January - 1967 April (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, circa 1983 (Box 18)
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: "Saltimbanques," translation by A. Poulin, unbound copy, signed (Box 18)
      - Science fiction, notes for a class on (Box 18)
      - "The Widow's Taboo," correspondence and typescript (Box 18)
    - Waters, Michael: correspondence, manuscripts, circa 1974 (Box 18)
    - Wright, Franz: correspondence (Box 18)
    - Amorosi, Ray: correspondence, circa 1974 (Box 19)
    - Bell, Marvin
      - Correspondence (Box 19)
      - "The Escape Into You," typescript (copy), correspondence (Box 19)
    - E.P. Dutton & Co., Inc.: correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box 19)
    - Glück, Louise: correspondence and manuscripts (Box 19)
    - Kaufman, Shirley: correspondence and manuscripts (Box 19)
    - Koch, Kenneth
      - Interview by David Shapiro (Box 19)
        Includes Koch's corrections and comments, a letter from Shapiro regarding the interview, and letters from Koch regarding the interview and "Making In All Its Forms."
      - "The Pleasures of Peace," typescript (copy) (Box 19)
    - Lewisohn, James: correspondence, circa 1974 (Box 19)
    - Lieberman, Laurence: correspondence, circa 1974 (Box 19)
    - Logan, John: "The Zig-Zag Walls," typescript with comments by Walter Arnold, Logan's editor at E. P. Dutton (Box 19)
    - Nemerov, Howard: correspondence and manuscripts (Box 19)
    - Philips, Louis: "How Do You Dial a Crocodile?", inscribed (Box 19)
    - Plumly, Stanley: correspondence (Box 19)
    - Poulin, Al
      - American novel lectures, circa 1968-1969 (Box 19)
      - Correspondence regarding "Choice: A Gathering of New American Poets" (Box 19)
      - Correspondence regarding "Making In All Its Forms" (Box 19)
      - "F-C Translations" (Box 19)
      - Fiction, circa 1956-197? (Box 19)
      - Hébert, Anne: "Uncollected Poems," translation by A. Poulin, manuscript (Box 19)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, circa 1973-1974; 5 (Box 19)
      - Correspondence with publishers, circa 1975 (Box 19)
      - Correspondence with various individuals at SUNY / Brockport (Box 19)
      - Miscellaneous manuscripts, dates uncertain (Box 19)
      - Miscellaneous unpublished essays, circa 1960 (Box 19)
      - "A Momentary Order", 1978 (Box 19)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth: correspondence (Box 19)
    - Rosenthal, M. L.: correspondence (Box 19)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome: correspondence (Box 19)
    - Rutsala, Vern: correspondence (Box 19)
    - Schmitz, Dennis: correspondence and manuscripts (Box 19)
    - Shapiro, David: correspondence, circa 1974 (Box 19)
    - Stokes, Terry: correspondence, circa 1974 (Box 19)
    - Wagner, Linda: "The Assassination of Linda Wagner," bound typescript and correspondence (Box 19)
    - Aridjis, Homero: comments on (Box 20)
    - Byrne, Edward: correspondence (Box 20)
      Includes correspondence with John Ashbery.
    - Eberhart, Richard: correspondence and manuscripts (Box 20)
    - Gardner, Isabella: correspondence, circa 1981; 2 (Box 20)
    - Gioseffi, Daniela: correspondence, circa 1978-1983; 6 (Box 20)
    - Hall, Donald: correspondence, 1978-1983; 4 (Box 20)
    - Ignatow, David: correspondence, 1979-1983; 2 (Box 20)
    - Lane, William: "Catch Up Later," typescript, forward by Robert Bly; correspondence. (Box 20)
      Includes correspondence with Robert Bly.
    - MacLeish, Archibald: correspondence, circa 1982 (Box 20)
    - Makuck, Peter: correspondence, 1983-1984; 2 (Box 20)
    - Mathieu, Bertrand: correspondence, circa 1970-1984; 11 (Box 20)
    - Poulin, Al: correspondence regarding "Duino Elegies and Sonnets to Orpheus," reviews (Box 20)
    - Schaeffer, Susan Fromberg: correspondence, "Alphabet for the Lost Years," typescript, inscribed (Box 20)
    - Sexton, Anne: correspondence, published poetry, reviews (Box 20)
    - Bierman, Larry: correspondence (Box 21)
    - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence: "Open Eye, Open Mind," uncorrected proofs, photographs (Box 21)
    - Poulin, Al
      - Address book (Box 21)
      - "Contemporary American Poetry," manuscripts, notes, unbound copy, and miscellaneous material, 5 (Box 21)
      - Correspondence regarding poetry festival, 1974 (Box 21)
      - Hébert, Anne: "Poems," translation by A. Poulin, promotional material (Box 21)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1972-1978; 4 (Box 21)
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: "The Astonishment of Origins," translation by A. Poulin, proofs (Box 21)
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: "Duino Elegies and the Sonnets to Orpheus," translation by A. Poulin, promotional material, uncorrected proofs, 2 (Box 21)
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: "French Poems," translation by A. Poulin, typescript (Box 21)
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: translations by A. Poulin, manuscript and typescript (Box 21)
    - Selective Service System: correspondence (Box 21)
    - Center: NYSCA Applic., 1980-1981; 2 (Box 22)
    - Center budgets, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Center reports, 1980 (Box 22)
    - NYSCA, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Summer book fair (Box 22)
    - Explore Latin America, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Book fair info (Box 22)
    - Symposium plans (Box 22)
    - Board of Directors (Box 22)
    - NYSCA, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Center budgets, 1980-1981 (Box 22)
    - New York Writes (Box 22)
    - [Unidentified folder] (Box 22)
    - Community programs, 1979 (Box 22)
    - NYSCA task force (Box 22)
    - Center reports, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Upstate conference (Box 22)
    - NEA: general information (Box 22)
    - Center budgets, 1980-1981 (Box 22)
    - Center programs, 1980-1981 (Box 22)
    - Center checkbook, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Translation Workshop (Box 22)
    - Stafford residency (Box 22)
    - Symposium funding (Box 22)
    - Social charities registration (Box 22)
    - Poetry & Sense of Place, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Women and Literature, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Center: NYSCA Applic., 1979-1980 (Box 22)
    - Fund-raising consultants, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Educational programs, 1979 (Box 22)
    - TNYSLC: Interim Report, 1979 October (Box 22)
    - NY Council on Humanities (Box 22)
    - Foundation information (Box 22)
    - Laughlin Award (Box 22)
    - Symp. / Book Fair, 1980 (Box 22)
    - NEA (Box 22)
    - Board Meeting: agenda / minutes (Box 22)
    - Incorporation (Box 22)
    - Upstate Plans (Box 22)
    - Center: checkbook, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Center: cancelled checks (Box 22)
    - Manuscripts and versions, 1961-1971, undated; 12 (Box 23)
    - Making In All Its Forms, proofs and related material, 4 (Box 24)
    - Contemporary American Poetry, proofs and related material, 3 (Box 24)
    - [Contemporary American Poetry?], 4 (Box 25)
    - Poems: extra and/or revised copies, manuscripts (Box 25)
    - In Advent, manuscripts, 2 (Box 25)
    - Houghton-Mifflin promotional material (Box 25)
    - BOA Editions: financial records (Box 25)
    - "A Momentary Order," manuscript, 1978 (Box 25)
    - "The Singers," manuscript, 1977 June - 1978 August 11 (Box 25)
    - Manuscripts, 1972, 1978-1980; 6 (Box 25)
    - "Nameless Gardens" (Box 25)
    - In Advent, galleys, 3 (Box 26)
    - Unpublished essays, manuscripts (Box 26)
    - "Those Who Choose Life" (Box 26)
    - Making In All Its Forms, 2 (Box 26)
    - "Mary Hartman" (Box 26)
    - Anne Hébert translations (Box 26)
    - "Duino Elegies," final version / revisions, 1976 March 1 (Box 26)
    - "Baudelaire Journal", 1980 July 19 (Box 26)
    - Rilke: Taxes and Quatrains (Box 26)
    - Rilke: Orchards (Box 26)
    - Contemporary American Poets IV, correspondence with poets, 3 (Box 26)
    - Aridjis, Homero (Box 27)
    - Byrne, Edward (Box 27)
    - Friar, Kimon (Box 27)
    - Gardner, Isabella, 2 (Box 27)
    - Gioseffi, Daniela, 2 (Box 27)
    - Hall, Donald: "The Toy Bone" (Box 27)
    - Ignatow, David (Box 27)
    - Logan, John, 3 (Box 27)
    - Tribute to Logan book (Box 27)
    - Makuck, Peter, including "Where We Live", 3 (Box 27)
    - Mathieu, Bertrand, 3 (Box 27)
    - Mills, Ralph J., Jr., 3 (Box 27)
    - Piccione, Arthur: "Anchor Dragging", 2 (Box 27)
    - Rosenthal, M. L. (Box 27)
    - Simpson, Louis: "People Live Here", 2 (Box 27)
    - School papers, essays, and plays, 37 (Box 28)
    - BOA Editions material related to NEA and NYSCA, financial records, and rejects, circa 1982-1984; 12 (Box 29)
    - In Advent, typescript (copies) (Box 29)
    - Unidentified manuscripts, circa1961-1971; 15 (Box 30)
    - Cendrars Xmas Stories (Box 31)
    - "Where We Live," corrected galleys (Box 31)
    - "The Whale," corrected galleys (Box 31)
    - "Signatures," corrected galleys (Box 31)
    - "Whomp & Moonshiver," corrected galleys (Box 31)
    - "That Was Then," uncorrected galleys (Box 31)
    - Schaeffer (Box 31)
    - Stone, Alan: "Verlaine: Women and Men," translation, 1978 (Box 31)
    - "Erotocritos," translation, 4 (Box 31)
    - Kizer, Carolyn: "Yin," typescripts and proofs, 6 (Box 31)
    - Poulin, A.: "A Momentary Order," typescript (Box 31)
    - Simpson, Louis: "People Live Here," typescripts and proofs, 3 (Box 31)
    - Friar (Box 31)
    - J. Tsatos (Box 31)
    - Manuscripts, 2 (Box 31)
    - Poems - Duplicates (Box 31)
    - Contemporary American Poets, 3rd edition, drafts, deleted material, and galleys, circa 1979; 11 (Box 32)
    - American Poetry Review: correspondence, 1982 (Box 33)
    - "Baudelaire's Intimate Journals," first and second versions (Box 33)
    - CAP/YAP Questionnaires (Box 33)
    - Contemporary American Poetry IV: correspondence with photographers (Box 33)
    - Contemporary American Poetry IV: correspondence with publishers (Box 33)
    - Graywolf Press: correspondence, 1981-1982; 2 (Box 33)
    - Harper, Michael: "Healing Songs for the Inner Ear" (Box 33)
    - Kayalis, Takis: correspondence and essays, 1982-1983; 4 (Box 33)
    - Logan, John: correspondence and poems, 2 (Box 33)
    - Poulin, Al: correspondence, 1983-1984; 4 (Box 33)
    - Sadowick, Douglas: dissertation, poems, prose (Box 33)
    - Schultz, Philip: "Deep Within the Ravine" (Box 33)
    - Simpson, Louis: Interview with (Box 33)
    - Stern, Gerald: "Paradise Poems" (Box 33)
    - Publications and rejections, 1982 (Box 33)
    - Houghton Mifflin Trade correspondence, 1982 (Box 33)
    - Inquiries to publishers, 1981-1982; 2 (Box 33)
    - Readings, 1982 (Box 33)
    - Magazine rejections/acceptance, 1982 (Box 33)
    - HMC, 1981 (Box 33)
    - Agents, 1981 (Box 33)
    - Notes for essays, lectures, reviews (Box 33)
    - Versions, typescripts, 2 (Box 34)
    - Printed material, 2 (Box 34)
    - Contemporary American poetry IV, Notes on Poets (Box 34)
    - Symposium - speeches only / bibliography, 1963 (Box 34)
    - Integrated Core Program (Box 34)
    - Idea for Symposium (Box 34)
    - SFC Programs (Box 34)
    - Symposium - Publicity, 1964 (Box 34)
    - Books for symposium (Box 34)
    - Symposium correspondence, 1964 (Box 34)
    - Symposium - open plans (Box 34)
    - Symposium manuscript, 1963 (Box 34)
    - Symposium protest (Box 34)
    - Al Theroux (Box 34)
    - Analysis (Box 34)
    - Edward Jellow (Box 34)
    - Ignatow, David: "The Notebooks of David Ignatow," proof (copy) (Box 35)
    - Logan, John and Caplin, Bill: "Dialogues on Literature and Psychology" from taped conversations, 1972 (Box 35)
    - Poulin, Al
      - Rilke, Rainer Maria: "The Astonishment of Origins," H. B.'s comments, and other translations by Poulin, 2 (Box 35)
      - Contemporary American Poetry, galley proofs and cover proofs, 5 (Box 35)
    - Printed material, 2 (Box 35)
    - Wilbur, Richard: "Walking to Sleep," uncorrected proofs (Box 35)
    - Unsorted material (Box 36)
  - Audiovisual Material
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Reel-to-reel Tapes
      Box 37: Restricted Fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - "A. Poulin, D. Sherwood, J. Logan" (1 of 3 reels), undated; 1; 1 7/8 speed (Box 37, Item barcode 39002091397068)